A Guide to the Rockefeller Foundation records, projects, RG 1.9-RG 1.15 (A83-A89) FA479
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Rockefeller Foundation records, projects (A 86), 1965-1991; bulk; 1.12; 67.2 Cubic Feet; 56 standard record storage boxes - Box R2305-R2360.
  - United States, 200
    - Rockefeller Archives & Research Center - (Minutes) (at RF), 1965-1979 1980 (Box R2327)
    - Rockefeller Archives & Research Center, 1976-1979 (Box R2327)
    - Rockefeller Archives & Research Center - Accessions (not inclusive), 1968-1979 (Box R2327)
    - Rockefeller Archives & Research Center - Archivist candidates, 1967-1968 1971-1972 (Box R2327)
    - Rockefeller Archives & Research Center - Committees, 1966 1972-1973 (Box R2327)
    - Rockefeller Archives & Research Center - Construction, 1969 1972-1975 (Box R2327)
    - Rockefeller Archives & Research Center - Counsel, 1969 1973 (Box R2327)
    - Rockefeller Archives & Research Center - Ernst, 1965-1968 1971 (Box R2327)
    - Rockefeller Archives & Research Center - Organization and planning, 1957-1975 (Box R2327)
    - Rockefeller Archives & Research Center - Organization and planning - Reports (Box R2327)
    - Rockefeller Archives & Research Center - Posner, 1966-1967 (Box R2327)
    - Rockefeller Archives & Research Center - Transfer of Records, 1967-1980 (Box R2327)
    - Rockefeller Archives & Research Center - Transfer of Records - Peking Union Med. College (Box R2327)
    - Saks, Daniel H., 1982-1985 (Box R2328)
    - Social Science Research Council - Southeast Asian conference, 1982-1984 (Box R2328)
    - Southern Education Foundation - Education & public policy, 1982-1984 (Box R2328)
    - Southern Regional Council - State race and poverty maps, 1982-1985 (Box R2328)
    - State University of New York at Plattsburgh - Agrarian conference, 1983-1985 (Box R2328)
    - Town Hall Foundation, Inc., 1983-1985 (Box R2328)
    - University of Denver - African development conference, 1984 (Box R2328)
    - University of Wisconsin - South Asian film, 1982-1985 (Box R2328)
    - Vanderbilt University - Latin American conf., 1983-1984 (Box R2328)
    - Wider Opportunities for Women - Computerized system, 1983-1985 (Box R2328)
    - Women, Households and Human Capital Formation - Conference, 1982-1983 (Box R2328)
    - Working Women Education Fund - Conference proceedings, 1983-1985 (Box R2329)
    - United States - Medical Sciences, A
      - Center for Disease Control - Family planning evaluation - Chen, 1983-1984 (Box R2329)
      - Center for Disease Control - Family planning evaluation - Franco, 1983-1984 (Box R2329)
      - Center for Disease Control - Family planning evaluation - Park, 1982-1985 (Box R2329)
      - Center for Disease Control - Family planning evaluation - Vibal-Fermo, 1982-1983 (Box R2329)
      - Chang, K.P., 1982-1984 (Box R2329)
      - Chaplan, Sandra, 1984 (Box R2329)
      - Clough, Ellen R., 1983-1984 (Box R2329)
      - Harvard University - Medical education conference, 1980-1981 (Box R2329)
      - Harvard University - Statistics, 1979-1985 (Box R2329)
      - International Health & Biomedicine, Ltd. - "Sharp compassion", 1983-1984 (Box R2329)
      - North American Primary Care Research Group, 1980-1985 (Box R2329)
      - Program for Appropriate Technology in Health, 1982-1984 (Box R2329)
      - Rockefeller University - Genomic clone, 1983 (Box R2329)
      - Salk Institute for Biological Studies - Peptide research, 1979-1984 (Box R2329)
      - University of North Carolina - Epidemiological training, 1982-1985 (Box R2329)
      - University of Wisconsin - Tracy, 1983-1985 (Box R2330)
      - Yeshiva University - Magnetic resonance & parasitism conference, 1984-1985 (Box R2330)
    - United States - Natural Sciences and Agriculture, D
      - Boyce Thompson Institute - Molecular genetics conference, 1984-1985 (Box R2330)
      - Cornell University - Maize resistance, 1974-1984 [?] (Box R2330)
      - Monell Chemical Senses Center - Fish, 1981-1985 (Box R2330)
      - Oklahoma State University - Anaplasmosis, 1983-1985 (Box R2330)
      - Pennsylvania State University - Pest management, 1980-1984 (Box R2330)
    - United States - Fellowships, Scholarships and Training Awards, E
      - Eff, Elaine, 1978-1985 [?] (Box R2330)
      - Paulson, Jo Ann, 1978-1985 (Box R2330)
    - United States - Population Sciences, P
      - Center for Women's Studies and Services - Project choice, 1980-1984 [?] (Box R2331)
      - Cornell University - Norethindrone, 1982-1985 (Box R2331)
      - Dryfoos, Joy, 1981-1985 (Box R2331)
      - Global Committee of Parliamentarians - Conference, 1984-1985 (Box R2331)
      - Johns Hopkins University - Adolescent sexuality, 1981-1986 (Box R2331)
      - Marine Biological Laboratory - Conch recruitment, 1981-1984 (Box R2331)
      - Mertens, Walter, 1983-1985 (Box R2331)
      - Population Institute - Target, 1990 1982-1984 (Box R2332)
      - Temple University - Chinese scientists training, 1981-1985 (Box R2332)
      - University of Michigan - Noppavan, 1983-1984 (Box R2332)
      - University of Nebraska - Fertilization study, 1932-1985 (Box R2332)
      - University of Texas - Relaxin study, 1981-1984 (Box R2332)
    - United States - Humanities and Arts, R
      - American Assembly - Arts & public policy conference, 1982-1985 (Box R2332)
      - American Council for the Arts - Artist in America task force, 1984-1985 (Box R2332)
      - American Historical Association - Constitutional history, 1983-1984 (Box R2332)
      - Asia Society - Encyclopedia of Asian history, 1982-1985 (Box R2332)
      - Association of Former Members of Congress - Humanities programming, 1982-1985 (Box R2332)
      - Aurora Music Foundation - Glass, 1980-1985 (Box R2332)
      - California Institute of the Arts - Padua Hills writers' workshop, 1984-1985 (Box R2333)
      - Carter Family Memorial Music Center - Recording, 1981-1984 (Box R2333)
      - Claremont University Center - Humanities program, 1982-1986 (Box R2333)
      - Corporation for Public Broadcasting - International screening conference, 1979-1983 (Box R2333)
      - Corporation for Public Broadcasting - International screening conference & supp. material, 1977-1978 (Box R2334)
      - Dances We Dance - "Invention"[?], 1983-1984 (Box R2335)
      - Educational Broadcasting Corp. - "Good Morning, Mr. Orwell", 1983-1985 (Box R2335)
      - Elgin Theater Foundation, 1979-1985 (Box R2335)
      - Gay, Peter, 1982-1985 (Box R2335)
      - Gibson, Jan, 1981-1985 (Box R2335)
      - Ginsberg, Allen, 1981-1984 (Box R2335)
      - Global Perspectives in Education - Social studies & foreign language teachers, 1983-1985 (Box R2336)
      - Guadalupe Cultural Arts Center - Cine festival, 1982-1984 (Box R2336)
      - Harvard University - Coles, 1977-1983 (Box R2336)
      - Harvard University - Revolutionary China conference, 1982-1984 (Box R2336)
      - Hays, Ron, 1977-1984 (Box R2336)
      - Hexter, Jack, 1982-1985 (Box R2336)
      - Institute for Research in History - Eleanor Roosevelt anthology, 1983-1985 (Box R2337)
      - Journal of Interdisciplinary History - Art & social history workshops, 1983-1984 (Box R2337)
      - La Mama Experimental Theatre Club - American-African arts exchange, 1982-1984 (Box R2337)
      - Marable, Manning, 1978-1982 (Box R2337)
      - Modern Language Association - English teaching conference, 1984-1985 (Box R2337)
      - Museum of Fine Arts, Houston - Krasner retrospective, 1982-1985 (Box R2337)
      - National Humanities Alliance - Humanities report, 1983-1986 (Box R2337)
      - National Humanities Center - Fellowships, 1974-1984 (Box R2338)
      - National Humanities Faculty - Teacher training institute, 1983-1985 (Box R2338)
      - New School of Social Research - Myth in contemporary life conference, 1982-1985 (Box R2338)
      - Nikolais/Louis Foundation for Dance - Film editing, 1981-1984 (Box R2338)
      - Northwestern University - Medical school faculty, 1981-1982 1985 (Box R2338)
      - Pomona College - Padua Hills writers workshop, 1981-1983 (Box R2339)
      - Puerto Rican Traveling Theater Co. - Playwrights unit, 1978-1985 (Box R2339)
      - Reise, Jay, 1981-1983 (Box R2339)
      - Robins, Kenneth, 1982-1984 (Box R2339)
      - Rutgers University - Literature and urban experience, 1978-1983 (Box R2339)
      - Rutgers University - Women state legislators film, 1983-1986 S (Box R2340)
      - Salzburg Seminar - Museum conference, 1983-1985 (Box R2340)
      - Sanborn, John, 1978-1985 (Box R2340)
      - Smith College - Women's history conf., 1983-1985 (Box R2340)
      - State University of New York - Black dance festival, 1982-1985 (Box R2340)
      - University of California - Museum studies (Berkeley), 1980-1984 S (Box R2340)
      - University of Maryland - Refugees and migrants rights, 1980-1984 (Box R2340)
      - University of Minnesota - Religion and revolution conf., 1981-1984 (Box R2340)
      - University of Pennsylvania - Humanities in public schools, 1983-1984 (Box R2341)
      - WGBH Educational Foundation - Philosophy television series, 1982-1984 (Box R2341)
    - United States - Social Sciences, S
      - University of Michigan - Panel study of income dynamics, 1981-1983 (Box R2341)
  - Equal Opportunity Projects, 277
    - National Policy Exchange - Employment and training, 1982-1985 (Box R2344)
    - New York City - Human Resources Admin. - Employment & welfare, 1983-1984 (Box R2344)
  - Latin America, 300
    - Latin America - Social Sciences, S
      - Latin American Social Science Research Council - Conference, 1982-1983 (Box R2344)
      - Latin American Social Science Research Council - Population policy, 1976-1985 (Box R2344)
      - Latin American Social Science Research Council - Population policy & suppl. mat., 1971-1975 (Box R2345)
      - Latin American Social Science Research Council - Population policy (suppl. material) (Box R2346)
  - Brazil, 305
    - Brazil - Medical Sciences, A
      - University de Rio Janeiro - Trypanosomiasis, 1979-1983 (Box R2347)
    - Brazil - Fellowships, Scholarships and Training Awards, E
      - Brito, Pedro Azevedo de, 1980-1983 (Box R2347)
      - Carmo Neto, Dionisio Gomes do, 1980-1984 (Box R2347)
      - Coelho, Isais, 1979-1983 1985 (Box R2347)
      - Franco Filho, Emmanuel, 1981-1984 (Box R2347)
      - Laudari, Carlos A., 1981-1983 1985 (Box R2347)
      - Lenzi, Henrique L., 1979-1983 (Box R2347)
      - Reesink, Marcelle, 1980-1983 (Box R2347)
    - Brazil - Population Sciences, P
      - CEMICAMP - Conference, 1984-1985 (Box R2347)
      - University of Bahia - Health effects of NORPLANT, 1981 1983-1985 (Box R2347)
  - Colombia, 311
    - Fundación para la Aplicación y Enseñanza de las Ciencias - Donation of equipment, 1983 (Box R2347)
    - Colombia - Humanities and Arts, R
      - Universidad del Valle - Humanities equipment, 1970-1977 1979-1982 1984 (Box R2347)
    - Colombia - Social Sciences, S
      - University of the Andes - Population studies, 1976-1986 S (Box R2348)
  - Costa Rica, 313
    - Costa Rica - Medical Sciences, A
      - University of Costa Rica - Field studies, 1981-1984 (Box R2349)
  - Ecuador, 317
    - Ecuador - Fellowships, Scholarships and Training Awards, E
      - Tola, Jaime E., 1979-1983 (Box R2349)
  - Guatemala, 319
    - Guatemala - Fellowships, Scholarships and Training Awards, E
      - Ruano Andrade, Sergio R., 1977-1984 (Box R2349)
  - Mexico, 323
    - Mexico - Fellowships, Scholarships and Training Awards, E
      - Esquivel Alvarez, Claudio, 1981-1985 (Box R2349)
      - Estrella-Chulin, Nestor, 1980-1984 (Box R2349)
      - Macias-Laylle, Joaquin A., 1980-1984 (Box R2349)
      - Villaipando I., Jose F., 1978-1984 (Box R2349)
    - Mexico - Population Sciences, P
      - Colegio de México - Demography fellowships, 1981-1985 (Box R2349)
      - Colegio de México - Population and development conf., 1983-1984 [?] (Box R2349)
  - Peru, 331
    - Peru - Medical Sciences, A
      - Bustamante, Ernesto, 1981-1985 (Box R2349)
    - Peru - Population Sciences, P
      - AMIDEP - Women and development workshop, 1981-1985 (Box R2350)
    - Peru - Social Sciences, S
      - Catholic University - Population fellowships, 1978-1981 (Box R2350)
  - Dominican Republic, 335
    - Dominican Republic - Social Sciences, S
      - Technological Institute of Santo Domingo - Population, 1977-1983 [?] (Box R2350)
  - England, 401
    - Science Policy Foundation - Change, 1982-1984 [?] (Box R2350)
    - England - Medical Sciences, A
      - Imperial College of Science and Technology - Helminths, 1982-1985 (Box R2351)
  - Australia, 410
    - Australia - Fellowships, Scholarships and Training Awards, E
      - Byers, Stephen W., 1980-1984 (Box R2351)
  - Canada, 427
    - Canada - Medical Sciences, A
      - Canadian Institute for Advanced Research - Population health, 1982-1984 (Box R2351)
      - University of Toronto - Filariasis, 1982-1985 (Box R2351)
      - University of Western Ontario - Family medicine, 1981-1983 (Box R2351)
      - University of Western Ontario - Medical care, 1980-1983 (Box R2351)
  - Ceylon, 462
    - Ceylon - Natural Sciences and Agriculture, D
      - Sarvodaya Shramadana Movement, 1980-1984 (Box R2351)
  - India, 464
    - India - Fellowships, Scholarships and Training Awards, E
      - Fernandez, Marilyn, 1981-1984 (Box R2351)
      - Gonsalves, Julian F., 1978-1984 (Box R2351)
      - Pakrasi, Pranab L., 1980-1984 (Box R2352)
      - Rao, M.R., 1982-1985 (Box R2352)
  - Bengal, 466
    - Bengal - Fellowships, Scholarships and Training Awards, E
      - Saha, Arun K., 1979-1984 (Box R2352)
  - China, 601
    - China - Medical Sciences, A
      - Information System for Medical Libraries - Conference, 1982 (Box R2353)
      - Sichuan Medical School - Health Services, 1981-1983 (Box R2353)
    - China - Fellowships, Scholarships and Training Awards, E
      - Chen Da-Yuan, 1980-1984 (Box R2353)
      - Guo Jian Zhong, 1981-1985 (Box R2353)
      - Lu, Gui-Shen, 1979-1983 (Box R2353)
      - Shen Xiao-Zhan, 1980-1983 1985 (Box R2353)
      - Shi Qi-Xian, 1981-1984 (Box R2353)
      - Tsong Shu-Dong, 1979-1981 (Box R2353)
      - Wang Linfang, 1979-1983 (Box R2353)
      - Zhang Chong-Li, 1980-1984 (Box R2353)
  - Japan, 609
    - Japan - Fellowships, Scholarships and Training Awards, E
      - Fukuoka, Hideoki, 1981-1983 (Box R2353)
      - Sato, Eimei, 1981-1984 (Box R2353)
      - Tanabe, Kiyoo, 1979-1982 1984 (Box R2353)
      - Tanaka, Toshinobu, 1980-1983 (Box R2354)
  - Korea, 613
    - Korea - Fellowships, Scholarships and Training Awards, E
      - Min, Kyonghee, 1981-1984 (Box R2354)
  - Thailand, 617
    - Thailand - Medical Sciences, A
      - Khon Kaen University - Chronic diseases, 1981-1984 (Box R2354)
    - Thailand - Natural Sciences and Agriculture, D
      - Kasetsart University - Food and agriculture policy, 1980-1986 [?] (Box R2354)
    - Thailand - Fellowships, Scholarships and Training Awards, E
      - Bhanupongse Nidhiprabha, 1979-1985 (Box R2355)
      - Bundit Jarimopas, 1978-1984 (Box R2355)
      - Charas Kitbamroong, 1980-1985 (Box R2355)
      - Chareinshuk Rajanaridpiched, 1979-1983 (Box R2355)
      - Chiradej Chamswarng, 1980-1984 (Box R2355)
      - Chinnaphong Bumrungsup, 1977-1985 (Box R2355)
      - Chucheep Piputisitee, 1978-1984 (Box R2355)
      - Jeerasak Pongissanupichit, 1974-1984 (Box R2355)
      - Sompop Kassuma, 1978-1985 (Box R2355)
      - Vuthiphong Priebjrivat, 1977-1985 (Box R2355)
  - ICLARM - International Center for Living Aquatic Resources Management, 626
    - Watanabe, Wade O., 1982-1985 (Box R2355)
  - Netherlands, 650
    - Netherlands - Medical Sciences, A
      - State University of Limburg - Conference, 1981-1984 (Box R2355)
  - Indonesia, 652
    - Indonesia - Fellowships, Scholarships and Training Awards, E
      - Azwar, Saifuddin, 1980-1983 (Box R2355)
      - Budiono, Santoso, 1979-1983 (Box R2355)
      - Mohtar, Mas'oed, 1978-1981 (Box R2356)
      - Nasrullah, Mr., 1978-1981 (Box R2356)
      - Setyawan Budiharta, 1978-1983 (Box R2356)
      - Soesanto Tjokrosonto (1st fellowship), 1976-1978 (Box R2356)
      - Woerjono Mangoendidjojo (1st & 2nd fellowships), 1973-1983 (Box R2356)
    - Indonesia - Humanities and Arts, R
      - Gadjah Mada University - Institute of Indonesian Cultural Studies, 1976-1984 (Box R2356)
    - Indonesia - University Development, UD
      - Gadjah Mada University - Agricultural station, 1975-1984 (Box R2356)
      - Gadjah Mada University - Community health programs, 1974-198[?] (Box R2356)
      - Gadjah Mada University - Donation of equipment, 1983 (Box R2357)
      - Gadjah Mada University - Filariasis, 1982-1983 (Box R2357)
      - Gadjah Mada University - Food production, 1981-1984 (Box R2357)
      - Gadjah Mada University - Goat production, 1977-1980 1982-1984 (Box R2357)
      - Gadjah Mada University - Medical staff development, 1975-198[?] (Box R2357)
      - Gadjah Mada University - Population Studies Institute, 1972-198[?] (Box R2357)
      - Gadjah Mada University - Poultry, 1977-1984 S (Box R2358)
      - Gadjah Mada University - Ruminant production, 1979-1985 S (Box R2358)
      - Gadjah Mada University - Student training, 1982-1984 (Box R2358)
  - Italy, 751
    - Italy - Population Sciences, P
      - University of Rome - Gonadatropin inhibitors, 1980-1984 (Box R2359)
  - Sweden, 800
    - Sweden - Population Sciences, P
      - University of Uppsala - Inhibition of progesterone, 1982-1984 (Box R2359)
  - Turkey, 805
    - Turkey - Natural Sciences and Agriculture, D
      - Foundation for Development Studies, 1979-1985 S (Box R2359)
    - Turkey - Fellowships, Scholarships and Training Awards, E
      - Aruoba, Celik, 1982-1984 (Box R2359)
      - Bulbul, Mehmet, 1981-1983 (Box R2360)
      - Sakar, Dogan, 1977-1983 (Box R2360)
    - Turkey - Social Sciences, S
      - Middle East Technological University - Agricultural price supports, 1979-1984 (Box R2360)
  - Egypt, 812
    - Egypt - Fellowships, Scholarships and Training Awards, E
      - El-Menabawey, Mohamed, 1979-1982 (Box R2360)
    - Egypt - Population Sciences, P
      - Al-Azhar University - Contraceptive implants, 1979-1985 (Box R2360)
      - Assiut University - Contraceptive implants, 1980-1985 (Box R2360)
      - Assiut University - Health effects of Norplant, 1981-1984 (Box R2360)
      - University of Alexandria - Contraceptive implants, 1980-1986 (Box R2360)
      - Zagazig University - Contraceptive implants, 1981-1985 (Box R2360)
  - Israel, 825
    - Israel - Medical Sciences, A
      - Mirelman, David, 1983-1985 (Box R2360)
  - Management Training Programs in Developing Countries, 850
    - Management Training Programs in Developing Countries - Venezuela, 339
      - Instituto de Estudios Superiores de Administración - Social development management, 1981-1984 (Box R2360)
- Rockefeller Foundation records, projects (A 87), 1978-1987; bulk; 1.13; 38.4 Cubic Feet; 32 standard record storage boxes - Box R2364-R2395.
  Files transferred to the RAC by Rockefeller Foundation, 1987.
  - Bellagio Study and Conference Center, 120
    - African Development Strategies - Conference, 1983-1985 (Box R2364)
    - Anhyrous Biology - Conference, 1984-1985 (Box R2364)
    - Art and History - Conference, 1983-1986 (Box R2364)
    - Calculus of Terror: Nuclear Strategy - Conference, 1984-1986 (Box R2364)
    - Causes of Backwardness in Eastern Europe - Conference, 1984-1985 (Box R2364)
    - Child Survival - Conference, 1981-1986 (Box R2364)
    - Conflicts & Non-violent Solutions - Conference, 1984-1985 (Box R2364)
    - Decentralized Educational Reform in Five Countries - Conference, 1984-1985 (Box R2364)
    - Detrital Systems for Aquaculture - Conference, 1981 1983-1985 (Box R2364)
    - Evolution of Law within Specific Societies - Conference, 1984-1985 (Box R2364)
    - Food Policy Impact - Conference, 1983-1985 (Box R2364)
    - Foreign Language and International Studies - Conference, 1983-1986 (Box R2364)
    - Future of Health and Health Systems in the Industrialized Societies - Conference, 1983-1986 (Box R2364)
    - Future of Peacekeeping - Conference (not held), 1983-1984 (Box R2364)
    - Gender & Political Culture in the Age of Democratic Revolution - Conference, 1984-1986 (Box R2365)
    - Good health at Low Cost - Conference, 1984-1986 (Box R2365)
    - Health Statistics in the Year 2000 - Conference, 1982-1984 (Box R2365)
    - Immunomodulation - Conference, 1983-1985 (Box R2365)
    - Infectious Plant Disease - Conference, 1984-1986 (Box R2365)
    - International Banking & Industrial Finance - Conference, 1982-1985 (Box R2365)
    - International Education - Conference, 1984-1986 (Box R2365)
    - International Migration - Conference, 1984-1985 (Box R2365)
    - Intra-ovarian Control Mechanisms - Conference, 1979-1983 1986 (Box R2365)
    - Jewish Literature - Conference, 1981-1984 (Box R2365)
    - Judicial and Legal Elites - Conference, 1984-1985 (Box R2366)
    - National Food Policy - Conference, 1981-1983 [?] (Box R2366)
    - Nuclear Arms Control - Conference, 1984-1985 (Box R2366)
    - Nutrition and Families - Conference, 1984-1986 (Box R2366)
    - Parliamentary Government in Contemporary Western Europe - Conference (not held), 1984-1985 (Box R2366)
    - Post-Nairobi Women & Development - Conference, 1985-1986 (Box R2366)
    - Psychology of Soviet-American Relations - Conference, 1984-1986 (Box R2366)
    - Reflections on Development - Conference, 1983-1986 (Box R2366)
    - Research Priorities in Sub-Saharan Africa - Conference, 1984-1985 (Box R2366)
    - Scholars - Allen, 1983-1986 (Box R2366)
    - Scholars - Barnes, M.J., 1982-1985 (Box R2366)
    - Scholars - Beall, 1984-1986 (Box R2366)
    - Scholars - Bell, L.T., 1984-1986 (Box R2367)
    - Scholars - Bettelheim, B., 1983-1985 (Box R2367)
    - Scholars - Birch, A.H., 1983-1987 (Box R2367)
    - Scholars - Bleikasten, A., 1984-1986 (Box R2367)
    - Scholars - Botkin, D., 1985-1986 (Box R2367)
    - Scholars - Burns, J.M., 1984-1985 (Box R2367)
    - Scholars - Burton, S., 1984-1986 (Box R2367)
    - Scholars - Busby, G., 1984-1985 (Box R2367)
    - Scholars - Buvinic, M., 1984-1986 (Box R2367)
    - Scholars - Checkland, O., 1984-1985 (Box R2367)
    - Scholars - Checkland, S.G., 1982 1984-1985 (Box R2367)
    - Scholars - Clark, D., 1984-1985 (Box R2367)
    - Scholars - Claude, 1984-1986 (Box R2367)
    - Scholars - Clausen, 1984-1985 (Box R2367)
    - Scholars - Constable, 1984-1985 (Box R2367)
    - Scholars - Coppola, C., 1983-1985 (Box R2367)
    - Scholars - Crichton, 1984-1986 (Box R2367)
    - Scholars - Dolezelova-Velingerova, 1984-1985 (Box R2367)
    - Scholars - Fagles, 1983-1985 (Box R2367)
    - Scholars - Fane, 1984-1985 (Box R2367)
    - Scholars - Forer, 1984-1985 (Box R2368)
    - Scholars - Fox, P., 1984-1985 (Box R2368)
    - Scholars - Fuchs, L.H., 1984-1985 (Box R2368)
    - Scholars - Gelb, 1984-1986 (Box R2368)
    - Scholars - Georghiou, 1984-1985 (Box R2368)
    - Scholars - Gibian, 1984-1986 (Box R2368)
    - Scholars - Gottschalk, 1984-1986 (Box R2368)
    - Scholars - Hamburger, 1984-1986 (Box R2368)
    - Scholars - Harleman, 1984-1985 (Box R2368)
    - Scholars - Hoffman, 1984-1985 (Box R2368)
    - Scholars - Howze, 1984-1986 (Box R2368)
    - Scholars - Israel, 1984-1986 (Box R2368)
    - Scholars - Kallman, 1984-1986 (Box R2368)
    - Scholars - Kaplan, 1984-1985 (Box R2368)
    - Scholars - Kelman, 1984-1985 (Box R2368)
    - Scholars - Kodikara, 1984-1985 (Box R2368)
    - Scholars - Kolenda, P., 1984-1985 (Box R2368)
    - Scholars - Kovrig, B., 1983-1986 (Box R2369)
    - Scholars - Kramish, 1983-1984, 1986 (Box R2369)
    - Scholars - Korbonski, 1987 (Box R2369)
    - Scholars - Lamberton, 1984-1986 (Box R2369)
    - Scholars - Lea, 1984-1985 (Box R2369)
    - Scholars - Lefcourt, 1983-1985 (Box R2369)